<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lakurdina Articles</title><link>https://articles.lakurdina.com/</link><description>Recent content on Lakurdina Articles</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2022, Lakurdina; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 23:08:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://articles.lakurdina.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fire and Ice - a World Divided</title><link>https://articles.lakurdina.com/articles/2022/02/fire-and-ice-a-world-divided/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 23:08:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://articles.lakurdina.com/articles/2022/02/fire-and-ice-a-world-divided/</guid><description>Introduction Our World is divided. Nomatter how far back in history you go, it has always been the case that arguments will have two sides, and that people will take both of those sides with equal conviction. Our ability to do so is, arguably, one of the most important facets of our humanity, and is what differentiates us from many other gregarious species, such as sheep and wildebeest, for whom survival depends on consensus.</description></item><item><title>About Lakurdina Articles</title><link>https://articles.lakurdina.com/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://articles.lakurdina.com/about/</guid><description>Lakurdina Articles is Lakurdina&amp;rsquo;s main articles site. Here you will find articles on a wide variety of topics, from art and music through to astrophysics and organic chemistry.
This site relies heavily on work from contributors. We have a small number of regular contributors, but if you would like to provide content of any description that is also welcomed. For more information, please visit our contribute page.
Please note that this website is a work in progress, and the full range of articles, poems and stories is not yet present.</description></item><item><title>Contribute</title><link>https://articles.lakurdina.com/contribute/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:39:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://articles.lakurdina.com/contribute/</guid><description>I am very happy to consider contributions of articles for this site. The single criterion is that they must &amp;ldquo;make me think more than they make me swear&amp;rdquo;, not a big ask considering my peaceable nature and predilection for thinking.
Contributions of other material, such as poems and stories, are considered on the same basis.
If you think you can achieve this, and have work you would like to submit, please email contribute.</description></item></channel></rss>